{
    "id": "4c8e34196726417ca80302933822eae9",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you are really hungry, you can eat ……………… apple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She went on to become ………………….. successful playback singer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… library on the corner has an amazing collection of story books.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "An",
                "The"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t speak ………………… Hindi very well, but I can make myself understood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………… prettiest girl I have ever seen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where is ………………… cheese?’ ‘I ate it.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Move ………………… books off that chair and sit down.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… . Irish have their own language.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "An",
                "The",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. life is complicated.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The",
                "No article is needed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am writing ………………… book on Indian mythology.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}